<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Planta</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="post">POST</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="protein_n_n_protein_is_in_every_cell_of_the_body_it_is_used_to_build_and_repair_muscles_bone_skin_and_the_immune_system_we_also_need_it_to_make_hormones_and_enzymes_proteins_are_made_up_of_amino_acids_your_body_can_make_some_of_the_amino_acids_but_not_all_of_them_the_ones_your_body_cannot_make_are_called_essential_you_can_easily_meet_your_protein_needs_each_day_from_plant_foods_such_as_beans_peas_nuts_seeds_soy_products_whole_grains_and_vegetables_quinoa_a_seed_that_acts_like_a_grain_is_a_great_source_of_protein_and_all_the_essential_amino_acids_n_adults_need_about_0_36_grams_of_protein_per_pound_of_body_weight_a_day_multiply_your_weight_by_0_36_to_find_out_how_much_protein_you_need_for_example_if_you_weigh_160_pounds_160_x_0_36_about_58_grams_of_protein_a_day_n_n_vitimin_b12_n_n_your_body_needs_vitamin_b12_to_make_red_blood_cells_and_for_nerve_function_if_you_don_t_get_enough_b12_you_can_develop_anemia_or_nerve_damage_most_b12_comes_from_animal_foods_b12_is_found_in_nutritional_yeast_and_some_fortified_foods_such_as_n_n_cereals_n_meat_substitutes_n_rice_or_hemp_milk_n_n_read_labels_for_these_products_to_make_sure_b12_has_been_added_n_n_because_it_may_not_be_easy_to_get_enough_b12_from_fortified_foods_it_may_be_best_to_take_a_supplement_as_you_get_older_your_body_is_less_able_to_absorb_b12_your_physician_may_suggest_a_supplement_or_shot_to_help_prevent_a_deficiency_talk_with_your_physician_or_registered_dietitian_for_more_information_n_n_iron_n_n_iron_is_a_mineral_in_the_blood_that_carries_oxygen_getting_enough_iron_is_important_for_everyone_especially_pregnant_women_women_of_childbearing_age_children_and_infants_iron_rich_plant_foods_include_whole_grain_breads_and_cereals_dried_beans_and_peas_dark_green_leafy_vegetables_dried_fruits_nuts_and_seeds_some_foods_such_as_breakfast_cereals_are_fortified_with_iron_the_type_of_iron_found_in_plant_foods_is_not_absorbed_as_easily_as_the_iron_in_animal_products_however_eating_iron_rich_foods_along_with_vitamin_c_can_help_your_body_better_use_the_iron_some_foods_with_vitamin_c_are_oranges_mangos_kiwis_strawberries_red_peppers_tomatoes_broccoli_and_bok_choy_some_people_may_need_to_take_a_supplement_n_n_calcium_n_n_calcium_helps_build_bones_and_teeth_it_is_also_important_for_the_function_of_the_heart_muscles_and_nerves_good_sources_of_calcium_are_chinese_cabbage_bok_choy_kale_calcium_set_tofu_and_broccoli_there_are_also_many_calcium_fortified_foods_such_as_soy_or_almond_milk_and_cereal_n_n_zinc_n_n_zinc_is_important_for_the_immune_system_wound_healing_and_blood_sugar_control_good_sources_are_whole_grains_tofu_tempeh_beans_peas_lentils_nuts_seeds_and_fortified_breakfast_cereals_compounds_in_plant_foods_called_phytates_keep_zinc_from_being_absorbed_this_can_be_improved_by_soaking_beans_grains_and_seeds_in_water_for_several_hours_before_cooking_eating_sprouted_grains_and_beans_and_leavened_grains_such_as_bread_instead_of_crackers_also_increases_absorption_some_foods_are_fortified_with_zinc_n_n_vitamin_d_n_n_vitamin_d_is_needed_for_strong_bones_it_is_also_needed_for_muscles_and_nerves_and_the_immune_system_to_work_properly_very_few_foods_have_vitamin_d_we_get_most_of_our_vitamin_d_when_the_skin_is_exposed_to_the_sun_but_many_people_do_not_make_enough_from_sun_exposure_alone_some_foods_such_as_soy_or_almond_milk_and_cereal_have_added_vitamin_d_you_may_need_to_take_a_supplement_talk_with_your_physician_for_more_information_n_n_omega_3_fatty_acids_n_n_omega_3_fatty_acids_such_as_eicosapentaenoic_acid_epa_and_docosahexaenoic_acid_dha_found_in_fatty_fish_may_lower_the_risk_of_heart_disease_and_help_the_immune_system_and_brain_good_sources_of_plant_based_omega_3_fats_include_ground_flaxseeds_and_flaxseed_oil_walnuts_chia_seeds_and_organic_canola_oil_plant_based_omega_3s_dont_easily_convert_to_epa_and_dha_in_the_body_for_some_people_including_pregnant_women_or_people_with_chronic_health_conditions_taking_a_micro_algae_supplement_may_be_helpful_ask_your_physician_for_more_information">Protein \n \n Protein is in every cell of the body. It is used to build and repair muscles, bone, skin, and the immune system. We also need it to make hormones and enzymes. Proteins are made up of amino acids. Your body can make some of the amino acids, but not all of them. The ones your body cannot make are called essential. You can easily meet your protein needs each day from plant foods such as beans, peas, nuts, seeds, soy products, whole grains, and vegetables. Quinoa, a seed that acts like a grain, is a great source of protein and all the essential amino acids. \n Adults need about 0.36 grams of protein per pound of body weight a day. Multiply your weight by 0.36 to find out how much protein you need. For example, if you weigh 160 pounds: 160 x 0.36 = about 58 grams of protein a day. \n \n Vitimin B12 \n \n Your body needs vitamin B12 to make red blood cells and for nerve function. If you don\'t get enough B12, you can develop anemia or nerve damage. Most B12 comes from animal foods. B12 is found in nutritional yeast and some fortified foods such as: \n \n Cereals \n Meat substitutes \n Rice or hemp milk \n \n Read labels for these products to make sure B12 has been added. \n \n Because it may not be easy to get enough B12 from fortified foods, it may be best to take a supplement. As you get older, your body is less able to absorb B12. Your physician may suggest a supplement or shot to help prevent a deficiency. Talk with your physician or registered dietitian for more information. \n \n Iron \n \n Iron is a mineral in the blood that carries oxygen. Getting enough iron is important for everyone, especially pregnant women, women of childbearing age, children, and infants. Iron-rich plant foods include whole-grain breads and cereals, dried beans and peas, dark green leafy vegetables, dried fruits, nuts, and seeds. Some foods, such as breakfast cereals, are fortified with iron. The type of iron found in plant foods is not absorbed as easily as the iron in animal products. However, eating iron-rich foods along with vitamin C can help your body better use the iron. Some foods with vitamin C are oranges, mangos, kiwis, strawberries, red. peppers, tomatoes, broccoli, and bok choy. Some people may need. to take a supplement. \n \n Calcium \n \n Calcium helps build bones and teeth. It is also important for the function of the heart, muscles, and nerves. Good sources of calcium are Chinese cabbage, bok choy, kale, calcium-set tofu, and broccoli. There are also many calcium-fortified foods, such as soy or almond milk and cereal. \n \n Zinc \n \n Zinc is important for the immune system, wound healing, and blood sugar control. Good sources are whole grains, tofu, tempeh, beans, peas, lentils, nuts, seeds, and fortified breakfast cereals. Compounds in plant foods called phytates keep zinc from being absorbed. ‘This can be improved by soaking beans, grains, and seeds in water for several hours before cooking. Eating sprouted grains and beans, and leavened grains, such as bread, instead of crackers also increases absorption. Some foods are fortified with zinc. \n \n Vitamin D \n \n Vitamin D is needed for strong bones. It is also needed for muscles and nerves and the immune system to work properly. Very few foods have vitamin D, We get most of our vitamin D when the skin is exposed to the sun, but many people do not make enough from sun exposure alone. Some foods, such as soy or almond milk and cereal have added vitamin D. You may need to take a supplement. ‘Talk with your physician for more information. \n \n Omega-3 fatty acids \n \n Omega-3 fatty acids, such as eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA) and docosahexaenoic acid (DHA) found in fatty fish, may lower the risk of heart disease and help the immune system and brain. Good. sources of plant-based omega-3 fats include ground. flaxseeds and. flaxseed oil, walnuts, chia seeds, and organic canola oil. Plant-based omega-3s dont easily convert to EPA and DHA in the body. For some people, including pregnant women or people with chronic health conditions, taking a micro-algae supplement may be helpful. Ask your physician for more information.</string>
    <string name="non_starchy_vegetables_spinach_kale_swiss_chard_mustard_greens_collard_greens_broccoli_bok_choy_carrots_cauliflower_asparagus_green_beans_brussels_sprouts_celery_eggplant_mushrooms_onions_garlic_tomatoes_lettuce_sugar_snap_peas_summer_squash_peppers_artichoke_hearts_cabbage_cucumbers_n_n_starchy_vegetables_potatoes_yams_winter_squash_corn_green_peas_cassava_yuca_plantains_n_n_fruit_apples_oranges_bananas_berries_melon_papaya_grapes_mango_pineapple_kiwi_apricots_n_n_beans_peas_lentils_or_meat_alternatives_whole_foods_kidney_black_garbanzo_pinto_great_northern_and_adzuki_beans_lentils_edamame_green_soybeans_green_and_black_eyed_peas_tofu_tempeh_processed_processed_soy_or_other_protein_patties_or_links_choose_very_rarely_n_n_nuts_and_seeds_almonds_cashews_sunflower_seeds_walnuts_pistachios_flaxseeds_chia_seeds_nut_butter_n_n_whole_grains_bulgur_quinoa_oats_brown_or_wild_rice_buckwheat_barley_farro_whole_wheat_rye_millet_sorghum_processed_grains_whole_grain_bread_whole_grain_unsweetened_cereal_whole_wheat_tortillas_whole_wheat_pasta_n_n_fats_and_oils_avocados_olives_servings_processed_oils_canola_extra_virgin_olive_and_flaxseed_oil_n_n_dairy_alternatives_unsweetened_milks_0_2_such_as_soy_almond_rice_and_hemp_look_for_brands_fortified_with_vitamin_b12_soy_rice_and_almond_milk_cheeses_unsweetened_milks_0_2_such_as_soy_almond_rice_and_hemp_look_for_brands_fortified_with_vitamin_b12_soy_rice_and_almond_milk_cheeses_unsweetened_milks_0_2_such_as_soy_almond_rice_and_hemp_look_for_brands_fortified_with_vitamin_b12_soy_rice_and_almond_milk_cheeses_unsweetened_milks_0_2_such_as_soy_almond_rice_and_hemp_look_for_brands_fortified_with_vitamin_b12_soy_rice_and_almond_milk_cheeses">Non-Starchy Vegetables - Spinach, kale, Swiss chard, mustard greens, collard greens, broccoli, bok choy, carrots, cauliflower, asparagus, green beans, brussels sprouts, celery, eggplant, mushrooms, onions, garlic, tomatoes, lettuce, sugar snap peas, summer squash, peppers, artichoke hearts, cabbage, cucumbers \n \n Starchy Vegetables - Potatoes, yams, winter squash, corn, green peas, cassava (yuca), plantains \n \n Fruit - Apples, oranges, bananas, berries, melon, papaya, grapes, mango, pineapple, kiwi, apricots \n \n Beans, Peas, Lentils, or Meat Alternatives - Whole foods: Kidney, black, garbanzo, pinto, great northern, and adzuki beans; lentils; edamame (green soybeans); green and black-eyed peas; tofu; tempeh Processed: Processed soy or other protein patties or links (choose very rarely) \n \n Nuts and Seeds - Almonds, cashews, sunflower seeds, walnuts, pistachios, flaxseeds, chia seeds, nut butter \n \n Whole Grains - bulgur, quinoa, oats brown or wild rice, buckwheat, barley, farro, whole wheat, rye, millet, sorghum Processed grains: Whole-grain bread, whole-grain unsweetened. cereal, whole-wheat tortillas, whole-wheat pasta \n \n Fats and Oils - Avocados, olives servings Processed oils: Canola, extra virgin olive, and flaxseed oil \n \n Dairy Alternatives - Unsweetened milks, 0-2 such as soy, almond, rice, and hemp (look for brands fortified with vitamin B12); soy, rice, and almond milk cheeses Unsweetened milks, 0-2 such as soy, almond, rice, and hemp (look for brands fortified with vitamin B12); soy, rice, and almond milk cheeses Unsweetened milks, 0-2 such as soy, almond, rice, and hemp (look for brands fortified with vitamin B12); soy, rice, and almond milk cheeses Unsweetened milks, 0-2 such as soy, almond, rice, and hemp (look for brands fortified with vitamin B12); soy, rice, and almond milk cheeses</string>
    <string name="think_about_the_meatless_meals_you_already_cook_at_home_this_may_include_whole_wheat_pasta_with_marinara_sauce_black_beans_and_rice_or_lentil_soup_and_salad_n_n_change_a_favorite_recipe_to_be_plant_based_n_n_make_burritos_or_tacos_with_beans_rice_and_vegetables_without_the_meat_and_cheese_n_n_prepare_chili_with_beans_and_no_meat_n_n_replace_burgers_with_veggie_burgers_or_grilled_portobello_mushrooms_n_n_make_kebabs_with_vegetables_such_as_onions_bell_peppers_summer_squash_and_mushrooms_n_n_make_lentil_or_split_pea_soup_without_adding_meat_or_using_chicken_or_beef_broth_n_n_try_some_new_recipes_at_the_end_of_this_booklet_you_will_find_a_list_of_books_and_websites_that_have_recipes_you_can_try_you_can_also_get_cookbooks_from_your_local_library_or_kaiser_permanente_healthy_living_store_n_n_frozen_fruits_and_vegetables_are_an_easy_and_low_cost_way_to_eat_more_plants_when_you_cook_beans_from_scratch_the_quick_soak_method_can_help_remove_some_of_the_indigestible_sugars_that_cause_gas_n_n_put_the_beans_in_a_large_pot_and_cover_with_2_inches_of_water_bring_to_a_boil_for_3_minutes_n_n_cover_and_set_aside_for_1_to_4_hours_n_n_rinse_and_drain_well_n_n_make_sure_to_drink_plenty_of_water_it_is_best_to_avoid_juice_soda_and_other_sugary_drinks_n_n_choose_organic_foods_when_possible_especially_corn_vegetables_fruits_and_soy_products_n_n_check_out_a_local_farmers_market_for_good_deals_on_produce_sometimes_cooking_plant_based_meals_can_take_more_time_to_save_time_n_n_make_a_larger_pot_of_beans_or_lentils_and_freeze_some_for_later_buy_precut_fresh_or_frozen_vegetables_n_n_buy_precooked_grains_such_as_barley_farro_or_brown_and_wild_rice_n_n_when_baking_yams_or_potatoes_make_a_few_extra_to_use_in_the_next_meal_n_n_use_canned_beans_including_nonfat_refried_beans_n_n_try_firm_tofu_cut_in_slices_and_seasoned_with_spices_and_green_onions_n_n_if_your_family_is_not_following_a_plant_based_diet_with_you_n_n_cook_meat_separately_and_add_it_to_the_other_plant_based_foods_n_n_encourage_your_family_to_try_more_meatless_meals_n_n_try_new_recipes_they_might_enjoy_such_as_five_bean_chili_without_meat_or_portobello_mushroom_burgers_n_n_you_might_need_to_add_a_few_items_to_your_kitchen_including_n_n_a_good_chef_s_knife_to_cut_vegetables_fruits_and_other_plant_based_foods_n_n_a_blender_or_food_processor_n_n_a_large_pot_pressure_cooker_or_crockpot_to_cook_beans">Think about the meatless meals you already cook at home. This may include whole-wheat pasta with marinara sauce; black beans and rice; or lentil soup and salad. \n\n Change a favorite recipe to be plant-based. \n\n -Make burritos or tacos with beans, rice, and vegetables without the meat and cheese. \n\n -Prepare chili with beans and no meat. \n\n -Replace burgers with veggie burgers or grilled portobello mushrooms. \n\n -Make kebabs with vegetables such as onions, bell peppers, summer squash, and mushrooms. \n\n -Make lentil or split pea soup without adding meat or using chicken or beef broth. \n\n Try some new recipes. At the end of this booklet you will find a list of books and websites that have recipes you can try. You can also get cookbooks from your local library or Kaiser Permanente Healthy Living Store. \n\n Frozen fruits and vegetables are an easy and low-cost way to eat more plants. When you cook beans from scratch, the quick-soak method can help remove some of the indigestible sugars that cause gas. \n\n Put the beans in a large pot and cover with 2 inches of water. Bring to a boil for 3 minutes. \n\n -Cover and set aside for 1 to 4 hours. \n\n -Rinse and drain well. \n\n Make sure to drink plenty of water. It is best to avoid juice, soda, and other sugary drinks. \n\n Choose organic foods when possible, especially corn, vegetables, fruits, and soy products. \n\n Check out a local farmers market for good deals on produce. Sometimes, cooking plant-based meals can take more time. To save time: \n\n -Make a larger pot of beans or lentils and freeze some for later. Buy precut fresh or frozen vegetables. \n\n -Buy precooked grains, such as barley, farro, or brown and wild rice. \n\n -When baking yams or potatoes, make a few extra to use in the next meal. \n\n -Use canned beans, including nonfat refried beans. \n\n -Try firm tofu cut in slices and seasoned with spices and green onions. \n\n If your family is not following a plant-based diet with you: \n\n -Cook meat separately and add it to the other plant-based. foods. \n\n -Encourage your family to try more meatless meals. \n\n -Try new recipes they might enjoy, such as five-bean chili without meat or portobello mushroom burgers. \n\n You might need to add a few items to your kitchen, including: \n\n -A good chef’s knife to cut vegetables, fruits, and other plant-based foods \n\n -A blender or food processor \n\n -A large pot, pressure cooker, or crockpot to cook beans</string>
    <string name="tips_tricks_when_that_every_person_should_know_to_make_thier_transition_an_easier_process"><![CDATA[Tips & tricks when that every person should know to make thier transition an easier process]]></string>
    <string name="tips_tricks"><![CDATA[Tips & Tricks]]></string>
    <string name="tips_tricks1"><![CDATA[Tips & Tricks]]></string>

</resources>